One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
You don't want us to open the country either.
‫أنتم أيضًا لا تريدون فتح هذه البلاد‬
Right?
‫صحيح؟‬
Because in order to fight pirates, you buy weapons from pirates.
‫لأنكم تريدون شراء الأسلحة من القراصنة لتقاتلوا قراصنة آخرين‬
Don't you find it strange?
‫هذا غريب...‬
Hmm?!
‫أليس كذلك؟‬
With your broker Doflamingo, also known as Joker, out of the picture,
‫بعد اعتقال وسيطكم دوفلامينغو الملقب بالجوكر‬
you have no choice but to trade with us directly.
‫فقدتم الستار الذي تختبئون خلفه واضطررتم إلى التفاوض معي مباشرة‬
I know you're out on a limb, so the advantage is mine...
‫أنتم في موقف يائس، وأنا فقط أحاول الحصول على أفضل صفقة‬
And already your demands are unreasonable.
‫مع ذلك، أنت تطلب منا الكثير‬
Look, Wano is entirely self-sufficient!
‫بلاد وانو مكتفية ذاتيًّا‬
Everyone here seems happy, right?
‫ألا ترون مدى سعادة سكان البلاد؟‬
If there is something we need, that would be greater power!
‫إن كنت أحتاج منكم شيئًا، فهو مزيد من مواضع القوة‬
This time, I'm only asking for a warship...
‫طلبي هذه المرة سفينة حربية فقط‬
Next time, I'll want Dr. Vegapunk!
‫ولكن في المرة القادمة، سيكون الدكتور فيغابانك‬
That's impossible!
‫هذا مستحيل‬
I didn't ask if it's possible!
‫لم أسألك عن استحالة طلبي من عدمه‬
The Celestial Dragons? The Marines?
‫التنانين السماوية؟ البحرية؟‬
You know we're not afraid of them, right?
‫أنتم تعرفون حق المعرفة أننا لا نخشاهم، صحيح؟‬
You couldn't bring us down even if you all banded together.
‫لا يمكنكم إسقاط هذه البلاد حتى لو اجتمعت كل قواتكم‬
I have Kaido backing me after all!
‫فأنا لدي كايدو يدعمني‬
One Piece
‫ون بيس‬
Wano Arc
‫آرك وانو‬
Oiran Komurasaki Arrives
‫وصول الأويران كوموراساكي‬
Komurasaki the top oiran is in procession!
‫افسحوا الطريق لموكب المحظية المرموقة كوموراساكي‬
Oh, Lady Komuraski!
‫كوموراساكي-ساما‬
Look over here, Oiran!
‫انظري إلينا أيتها الأويران‬
I'm sorry I'm late!
‫اعذري تأخري‬
I was worried about you.
‫قلقت عليكِ‬
Please forgive me, Big Sis!
‫اعذريني يا أختاه‬
Now, get to work.
‫باشري العمل‬
Okay!
‫حاضرة‬
Here comes Lady Komurasaki!
‫ها قد أتت كوموراساكي-ساما‬
It's the oiran's procession!
‫إنه موكب الأويران‬
Isn't she here yet?!
‫ألم تصل بعد؟‬
There're tons of people here.
‫يا له من جمعٍ كبير‬
I wonder how beautiful she is!
‫ما مدى جمالها يا تُرى؟‬
Please hurry, Komurasaki my beloved!
‫أسرعي يا كوموراساكي-تشوان‬
That conniving tramp...
‫أكره... تلك المرأة...‬
...Komurasaki!
‫كوموراساكي...‬
I think they're looking for trouble!
‫يبدو أنهم ينوون افتعال مشكلة‬
H-Hey!
‫مـ-مهلًا‬
I've got to...
‫لأقتلنّ...‬
kill that bitch!
‫تلك المرأة‬
It's all over!
‫انتهى أمري‬
If I'm gonna die,
‫إن كنتُ سأموت...‬
I'll take her with me!
‫فسآخذها معي‬
Stay away from the oiran!
‫لا تعترضوا موكب الأويران‬
Komurasaki...
‫كوموراساكي...‬
I want to be with you forever, my love...
‫أريد البقاء معك إلى الأبد‬
W-With an old geezer like me?!
‫تريدين البقاء مع عجوز مثلي؟‬
If I have to live Shogun Orochi's puppet...
‫إن كنتُ سأعيش جارية لأوروتشي-ساما‬
I would rather you bought out my contract...
‫فأُفضل أن تشتري عقدي‬
Alas, the price for my freedom is so outrageous,
‫ولكن مبلغ عتقي باهظ الثمن‬
Imagine if Shogun Orochi were to catch wind of this conversation.
‫إن عرف أوروتشي-ساما بما أخبرتك الآن، فحينها...‬
Don't fret, my dear!
‫لا تفقدي الأمل‬
If that is your desire,
‫إن كانت هذه رغبتك‬
I, Bingo, will make it happen!
‫أقسم أنا بينغو بتحقيقها لك‬
Really?
‫حقًّا؟‬
I'm glad to hear it, even if you're not serious.
‫حتى لو كنت تكذب، فقد أسعدتني‬
You don't have enough money to pay me back?!
‫لا تملكان مالًا يكفي لتسديد دينكما؟‬
I'm sorry!
‫سامحنا‬
Do you take me for a fool?!
‫هل أبدو لكما غبيًّا؟‬
You think crying will help?!
‫أتظنان أنّ البكاء سيجعلني أسامحكما؟‬
I'll take your house as collateral for the loan!
‫سآخذ منزلكما بدل المال‬
Here, Komurasaki.
‫تفضلي يا كوموراساكي‬
I've never seen so much money!
‫لم أرَ مبلغًا ضخمًا كهذا قط-أرينسو‬ ‫أرينسو: كلمة تقولها السيدات المرموقات والفاخرات‬
Komurasaki, here's an advance to buy you from the pleasure hall.
‫كوموراساكي، هذه دفعة مسبقة لعتقك من منطقة الملذات‬
It's not enough yet, but I want you to hold onto it.
‫أعلم أنها ليست كافية، ولكن احتفظي بها‬
Then, let me enter it in the ledger.
‫إذًا فلنوثّق هذه الدفعة دينًا بيننا‬
That's not necessary!
‫لا داعي لذلك‬
Only a fool mistrusts the woman he loves.
‫فقط الحمقى لا يثقون فيمن يحبونها‬
Your word is good enough for me.
‫وعدك يكفيني‬
My lord Bingo...
‫بينغو-ساما...‬
I cannot wait for the moment you take me with you.
‫لا يسعني انتظار اليوم الذي تأخذني فيه معك‬
Don't cry.
‫لا تبكي‬
It's all right!
‫لا بأس‬
I'll make the funeral arrangements.
‫سأقيم جنازة من أجلك‬
I'll also lend you some money for it and for living expenses.
‫وسأقرضك مالًا لتغطية مصاريفها ونفقات المعيشة‬
Stop crying already!
‫كفاكِ بكاءً‬
You need to pay me back double!
‫أصبحتِ مدينةً لي بالضعف الآن‬
It's your own fault for being so naive!
‫هذا ما اقترفته يداك بسبب سذاجتك‬
Here's your money!
‫تفضلي مالك‬
Wow! It's so much!
‫مذهل، مبلغٌ ضخم‬
But...
‫ولكن...‬
What's wrong?
‫ما الخطب؟‬
The truth is, someone else recently offered to buy my contract...
‫في الحقيقة، ثمة من قدّم عرضًا ضخمًا لشراء عقدي‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
I have to hurry!
‫بسرعة‬
I need more and more money to buy her... Is there anything that I can sell?
‫أحتاج مزيدًا من المال، أثمة ما يمكنني بيعه هنا؟‬
I sold my storehouse, Komurasaki!
‫بعتُ متجري يا كوموراساكي‬
I'm so grateful...
‫أنا ممتنةٌ لك‬
Enough is enough!
‫طفح الكيل‬
I'm fed up with you!
‫سئمت من تصرفاتك‬
I'm going back to my parents' house!
‫سأعود إلى منزل أهلي‬
Do whatever you like!
‫افعلي ما تشائين‬
I'm on my way, Komurasaki!
‫أنا قادم يا كوموراساكي‬
I've even abandoned my family!
‫تخليت عن عائلتي‬
Oh no, you must think of your health...
‫عليك الاهتمام بصحتك‬
Medicine is a waste of money.
‫الدواء هو ضياعٌ للمال‬
I'll be fine.
‫أنا بخير‬
Once I get what I want, I'll be the happiest man in the world.
‫سأغدو أسعد رجل في العالم حالما أظفر بكِ‬
I admit that I dream of my life with you every single night...
‫أحلم كل ليلة بحلول اليوم الذي نعيش فيه معًا تحت سقف واحد-أرينسو‬
Oh... Komurasaki!
‫أجل يا كوموراساكي‬
I got the last of it...
‫جمعت المبلغ المطلوب، لم أعد أملك منزلًا‬
I have the final 500 gold.
‫هذه آخر 500 قطعة ذهبية‬
With this, I can buy your contract, Komurasaki!
‫سأتمكن من شراء عقدك بهذا المبلغ يا كوموراساكي‬
I'm sorry. The oiran is sick today...
‫المعذرة، الأويران مريضة اليوم‬
Oh no!
‫يؤسفني سماع هذا‬
Just be sure to give her this. I'll be back later...
‫احرص على تسليمها هذا، سأعود لزيارتها لاحقًا‬
Komurasaki!
‫كوموراساكي‬
I've come to liberate you from the pleasure hall! Come live with me!
‫سأحررك من منطقة الملذات، لنعش معًا من الآن فصاعدًا‬
You really fell for it!
‫فعلتها حقًّا‬
Way to go, you old pervert!
‫أحسنت أيها العجوز المنحرف‬
Hey, guys!
‫أنتم‬
Quit laughing and get Komurasaki for me.
‫كفاكم ضحكًا واستدعوا كوموراساكي‬
She's going to live happily ever after with me!
‫ستعيش معي بسعادة وهناء‬
You moron! Dream on!
‫أحمق، كفاك أوهامًا‬
You have enough money to liberate her?
‫أتملك مالًا كافيًا لعتقها؟‬
Of course I do! Komurasaki already has it! I asked her to keep it safe for me!
‫بالطبع، إنه مع كوموراساكي، فقد طلبت منها الاحتفاظ به‬
Oh my... It's Mr. Bingo.
‫عجبًا، بينغو-سان‬
Oh, Komurasaki! Please set things straight!
‫كوموراساكي، أخبريهم بالحقيقة‬
They're running their mouths, completely unaware of our devotion to one another!
‫إنهم يضحكون لجهلهم بمدى جدية علاقتنا‬
Oh?
‫عجبًا‬
You gave me that money, did you not?
‫ألم تقل إنّ ذلك المال لي؟‬
I've already spent it all.
‫أنفقته كله‬
But thank you.
‫شكرًا لك‬
This old coot really thought Komurasaki was in love with him!
‫هذا العجوز صدّق أنّ كوموراساكي-سان واقعة في حبه‬
What's with the old fart?
‫من هذا الكهل...‬
Komurasaki...
‫يا كوموراساكي؟‬
B-Boss Kyoshiro!
‫الـ-الزعيم كيوشيرو‬
So...
‫عرفتك‬
you're the old man who's been hanging around Komurasaki these days...
‫أنت العجوز الذي يضايق كوموراساكي في الآونة الأخيرة‬
Hanging around...? L-Let me explain!
‫أضايقها؟ مستحيل‬
Komurasaki, this is a joke, right?
‫كوموراساكي، ألستِ تمزحين؟‬
I really did sacrifice all I had!
‫ضحيتُ بكل ما أملك‬
I don't have anything left!
‫لم أعد أملك شيئًا‬
I gave it all up for you!
‫تخليت عن كل شيء من أجلك‬
Well then...
‫بحق‬
How many of these saps has it been now?
‫كم أصبح عدد أمثاله الآن؟‬
We can't have you crying out here and obstructing business, old man.
‫أنت تعيق عملنا بصراخك هنا أيها العجوز‬
If you're done, beat it!
‫إن انتهيت، فارحل‬
You lecherous old geezer!
‫أيها العجوز الداعر‬
Stop!
‫توقفا‬
I'm leaving!
‫سأرحل‬
I'm leaving, so just stop!
‫سأرحل حالًا‬
Komurasaki...!
‫كوموراساكي...‬
Komurasaki the top oiran...
‫المحظية المرموقة كوموراساكي...‬
is in procession!
‫تسير في موكبها‬
Oiran Komurasaki Wano's Top Courtesan
‫الأويران كوموراساكي‬ ‫أجمل محظية في وانو‬
– Lady Komurasaki!
‫كوموراساكي-ساما‬
She's stunning!
‫عظيمة‬
She's gorgeous!
‫جمالها يأسر الأعين‬
Oh, she's beautiful...!
‫يا لجمالها‬
She's radiant! My eyes!
‫ضيائها يعمي الأبصار‬
Komurasaki!
‫كوموراساكي‬
I sold my house, my family, and everything else!
‫بعتُ منزلي عائلتي وكل ما أملك من أجلك‬
Give me back my money, you thief!
‫أعيدي إليّ مالي أيتها اللصة‬
Asking for your gift back?
‫أتطلبون مني إعادة هداياكم؟‬
What a pathetic display...
‫أليس هذا مثيرًا للشفقة؟‬
To me, men are just dogs who fetch me money.
‫في نظري، الرجال محض كلاب يجلبون إليّ المال‬
If you can't do that anymore, you're dead to me.
‫لا قيمة لهم عندي دون مال‬
Gentlemen, that's as far as you go!
‫لن تفلتوا من قبضتنا هذه المرة‬
If your wallets are empty, then get lost!
‫إياكم إثارة المتاعب أيها المفلسون‬
Anyone who can't generate wealth has no place in the Flower Capital.
‫لا يحق للفقراء العيش في عاصمة الزهور‬
In the name of Shogun Orochi, we'll expel you from the city!
‫باسم الشوغن أوروتشي، سننفيكم من العاصمة‬
Please don't!
‫توقفوا رجاءً‬
The conditions outside the city are inhumane!
‫لا يمكننا عيش حياة كريمة خارج العاصمة‬
Damn! Go to hell!
‫عليكِ اللعنة...‬
Komurasaki!
‫يا كوموراساكي‬
I have nothing but scorn...
‫ليس لدي سوى الازدراء...‬
for the poor.
‫للفقراء-أرينسو‬
Open the gate!
‫افتحوا البوابة‬
Komurasaki the top oiran has arrived!
‫وصلت المحظية كوموراساكي‬
So you have a little sister, Momo?
‫ألديك أخت صغيرة يا مومو-كن؟‬
Hey, Tama!
‫تاما‬
It is rude to address me so casually! Who do you think I am?!
‫إنكِ تتحدثين معي بوقاحة، ألا تعلمين من أنا؟‬
You're Momo.
‫أنت مومو-كن‬
Forget it.
‫انسي الأمر...‬
Yes, I have a little sister.
‫أجل، لدي أخت صغيرة‬
If she is alive, she would be twenty-six.
‫إن كانت حية، فسيكون عمرها الآن 26 سنة‬
There were witnesses to my mother's death, but no one has confirmed whether Hiyori died.
‫ثمة شهودٌ على موت أمي، ولكن لم يشهد أحد موت هيوري‬
So I have faith that she is still out there!
‫لذا أؤمن بأنها حية في مكانٍ ما‬
I hope you get to see her again.
‫آمل أن تراها مجددًا‬
Well, I won't!
‫كلا، لا يمكنني رؤيتها بعد‬
If her identity were to be exposed, Orochi would target her!
‫إن اكتشف أوروتشي هويتها الحقيقية، فسيستهدفها لا محالة‬
We will reunite only when the battle is won!
‫لا أريد مقابلتها إلا بعد انتصارنا بالمعركة‬
Kozuki Momonosuke Son of Wano's Late Daimyo of Kuri
‫كوزكي مومونوسكي‬ ‫ابن دايميو كوري الراحل‬
You think you can show up late to work because of some gorgeous oiran, Franko?!
‫أتظن الانبهار بجمال الأويران سببًا وجيهًا للتأخر عن العمل يا فرانكو؟‬
No, Boss!
‫كلا يا رئيس‬
I'm so sorry!
‫أرجو المعذرة‬
I mean, it's hard to believe such a beauty exists!
‫لكنها امرأة جميلة‬
I know how you feel!
‫أتفهم شعورك يا وغد‬
But you know I have my reputation to uphold, you dolt!
‫ولكن تأخرك قد يؤثر على سمعة تجارتي أيها الأحمق‬
Minatomo Legendary Master Carpenter The Man Who Built Kaido's Mansion
‫النجار المخضرم‬ ‫ميناتومو‬ ‫الرجل الذي بنى قصر كايدو‬
Yes! I'm so sorry!
‫أجل، أرجو المعذرة‬
I had no intention of bringing dishonor to the name of Minatomo, the legendary master carpenter!
‫لم أقصد تشويه سمعة النجار المخضرم ميناتومو‬
Since you put in ten times the amount of work than anyone else,
‫بما أنك تعمل أكثر من البقية بعشرة أضعاف‬
I guess I don't mind if you ditch work sometimes.
‫فلا أمانع إن تغيّبت عن العمل أحيانًا‬
If you show me the plans of the Onigashima stronghold you built,
‫إن أريتني مخططات حصن أونيغاشيما فسأعمل بمقدار عشرة أضعاف أخرى‬
No! A hundred times the amount of work!
‫لا، بل سأعمل بمقدار مئة ضعف‬
Oh, yeah.
‫نعم تذكرت‬
About those Onigashima mansion blueprints you keep asking me about...
‫مخططات قصر أونيغاشيما التي طالما طلبتها مني...‬
About those... Um...
‫إنها... لنرَ...‬
Oh, this is just a tissue.
‫هذا مجرد منديل‬
About those...
‫بشأن المخططات...‬
I just remembered...
‫تذكرت أمرًا...‬
I pawned them about ten years ago!
‫وهو أنني رهنتها قبل عشر سنوات‬
Why the hell do you think I've been working for you for all these weeks?!
‫لأي سبب تظنني عملت تحت إمرتك بجد طوال الأسابيع الماضية؟‬
Ouch! Damn it, cut it out, Franko!
‫توقف أيها الوغد فرانكو‬
You attacked your master! Who do you think you are?!
‫كيف تجرؤ على مهاجمة ربّ عملك؟‬
You blockhead!
‫أيها النجار الأبله‬
You're driving me crazy!
‫طفح كيلي منك‬
Eat this!
‫خذ هذه‬
Franosuke Rocket Launcher!
‫فرانوسكي روكيت لانشر‬ ‫قاذفات صواريخ فرانوسكي‬
You're fired! Get out of here, you simpleton!
‫كفى، أنت مطرود أيها الأحمق‬
Gladly! I no longer have business here anyway!
‫بكل سرور، فلم أعد أحتاج إلى العمل عندك‬
Pawn
‫متجر‬
Shop
‫رهنرهنرهنرهنرهن‬
Blueprints pawned ten years ago?
‫رُهنت قبل 10 سنوات؟ مخططات؟‬
It's rare that we would ever take those...
‫لكننا نادرًا تردنا أشياء كهذه‬
Oh, maybe those!
‫ربما عرفت ما تقصده‬
What? Do you have them?!
‫أيعقل أنها لديك؟‬
Well, of course, they've long since gone to somebody else...
‫كلا، فقد اشتراها أحد الزبائن بالطبع‬
Now, who would've bought such an item...?
‫ولكن يصعب عليّ تذكر من اشتراها‬
Hmm, who was it...?
‫من كان يا تُرى؟‬
Um...
‫لنرَ...‬
Oh, yeah!
‫تذكرت‬
It was Kumagoro from the tenements. He said he'd study them. No doubt about it!
‫لا شك أنه كوماغورو من عقار ناغايا، قال إنه يريد دراستها‬
Kumagoro From the Tenements
‫كوماغورو‬ ‫من عقار ناغايا‬
Who?!
‫من هذا؟‬
Kumagoro!
‫كوماغورو‬
Blueprints?
‫مخططات؟‬
Oh yeah, I had them at one point,
‫أجل، كانت معي فعلًا‬
but I fell behind on my rent, so my landlord Mr. Kobe took them.
‫لكنني تأخرت في دفع الإيجار وأخذها مالك العقار كوبي-سان‬
Kobe The Landlord
‫كوبي‬ ‫مالك العقار‬
Who the hell is that?
‫من هذا أيضًا؟‬
Rooms Available
‫شقق‬ ‫شاغرة‬
Kobe!
‫كوبي‬
Oh, the blueprints. They were of high quality, so I gave them to my favorite geisha.
‫تلك المخططات؟ كانت رائعة، لذا أعطيتها الغيشا المفضلة لدي‬
Miss Kisegawa.
‫كيسيغاوا-تشان‬
Kisegawa A Favored Geisha
‫كيسيغاوا‬ ‫غيشا مالك العقار المفضلة‬
Do you know her?
‫أتعرفها؟‬
No!
‫من هذه؟‬
I didn't know what to do with them, so I used them as a dish mat, but then Tokijiro...
‫كنت استخدمها سُفرةً تحت أطباق الطعام، ثم أعطيتها توكيجيرو-سان‬
Tokijiro
‫توكيجيرو‬
Okay, and who is that?
‫من هذا أيضًا بحق؟‬
I had them!
‫كانت بحوزتي‬
But the Camel said they could fetch a high price and took them!
‫لكن راكودا-سان أخذها قائلًا إنه سيبيعها بثمن باهظ‬ ‫ناقة‬
The Camel
‫راكودا‬
What? "The Camel"?! An animal did?!
‫راكودا؟ أليس هذا حيوان؟‬
They call me the Camel!
‫أنا راكودا‬
Man, those blueprints gave me nothing but trouble!
‫بحق، مررتُ بوقتٍ عصيب بسبب تلك المخططات‬
Some guy made off with them!
‫ثمة رجل سرقها مني‬
His face was covered, but he said he came from Kuri.
‫كان ملثّمًا، لكنه قال إنه من مقاطعة كوري‬
Kuri?!
‫كوري؟‬
Um...
‫عذرًا...‬
Oh, I'm sorry. It's sea bream.
‫معذرةً فقد لم أنتبه إليكِ، هذه سمكة الدنيس‬
Is that how sea bream usually looks?
‫أهكذا تبدو سمكة الدنيس؟‬
Nice doing business with you!
‫شكرًا لشرائك مني‬
Sir Franosuke!
‫فرانوسكي-دونو‬
You seem to be in high spirits.
‫تبدو بخير‬
Of course! But what in the world are you selling?
‫بالطبع، لكن ما الذي تفعله؟‬
What? Oh, I'm peddling fish.
‫ماذا؟ أنا أبيع السمك‬
You stick out like a sore thumb! Kids are drawn to you!
‫إنك ملفت للأنظار، الأطفال يتجمهرون حولك‬
Anyway, why were you in such a hurry? Is anything the matter?
‫الأهم الآن، لماذا كنت مستعجلًا قبل قليل؟ أثمة مشكلة؟‬
Oh, yeah! Forget sticking out! We've got bigger fish to fry!
‫صحيح، مشكلة لفتك للأنظار لا تقارن بحجم مشكلتي‬
The guy I thought had the blueprints didn't have them after all!
‫اتضح أن من أعمل عنده لا يملك المخططات‬
Check the swords over there next.
‫تحققوا تاليًا من السيوف هناك‬
What?! The blueprints for Kaido's mansion are here in Kuri?!
‫ماذا؟ مخططات قصر كايدو موجودة هنا في مقاطعة كوري؟‬
Yeah! I couldn't find them even after running all over the capital!
‫أجل، بحثت في جميع أنحاء العاصمة ولم أجدها‬
I'm not sure what I should do now!
‫بات وجودي في العاصمة مثل عدمه‬
I'm sorry you had to go through that.
‫أعتذر لتكليفك بمهمة عقيمة‬
Sir Franosuke, please help the others complete their missions in the capital.
‫فرانوسكي-دونو، ادعم بقية المهام في العاصمة‬
Got it!
‫مفهوم‬
Hmm... Who would want the blueprints of Kaido's mansion?
‫من عساه يرغب في مخططات قصر كايدو؟‬
Could it be...?
‫أيعقل أنه...‬
Your Grace! Sir Kin!
‫دوق-ساما وكين-سان‬
Look at all we stole! There's food and weapons from the factory!
‫استطعنا سرقة أسلحة من المصنع وكثيرًا من الطعام‬
Nice work. Did you leave the calling card?
‫أحسنتم، هل تركتم الرسالة؟‬
We sure did!
‫أجل، بالطبع‬
The Mount Atama Thieves were here. Shutenmaru
‫كان لصوص جبل أتاما هنا‬ ‫شوتينمارو‬
The Mount Atama Shutenmaru
‫شوتينمارو كان لصوص جبل أتاما هنا‬
But should we have?
‫ولكن ألا بأس بهذا؟‬
The note might cause the Beast Pirates to attack Ashura Doji.
‫بسبب الرسالة، قد يشن قراصنة الوحوش هجومًا على أشورا دوجي‬
That is what we want. Coming under attack will infuriate him.
‫هذا مبتغانا، لأنه سيغضب إن تعرض للهجوم‬
If we don't use his rage to goad him into fighting the Beast Pirates...
‫يمكننا بهذه الوسيلة حثّه على قتال قراصنة الوحوش‬
we'll never rekindle the fire within him.
‫عدا ذلك، لن يكون لديه دافع لقتالهم أبدًا‬
Considering the regret he's suffered for twenty years, this seems a bit heavy-handed.
‫تبدو وسيلة مجحفة حين أفكر بالمعاناة التي تجرّع مرارتها عشرين عام طِوَال‬
I know!
‫أعلم‬
But whether the means be fair or foul, we need him if we are to topple Kaido!
‫ولكن لا خيار آخر لدينا، فنحن نحتاج إليه لهزيمة كايدو‬
We need Ashura Doji's help!
‫نحن بحاجة إلى قوة أشورا دوجي‬
Hey! I'm back!
‫لقد عدت‬
Ebisu Town
‫بلدة إبيسو‬
Yasu!
‫ياسو-سان‬
Oh, you're back, Tonoyasu!
‫ها قد عدت يا تونوياسو‬
Yasu, you're back, but we still don't have any food!
‫ياسو-سان، أهلًا بعودتك لكننا لا نملك طعامًا لنقدّمه لك‬
I'm so hungry!
‫أنا جائع‬
I'm starving to death!
‫سأموت من شدة الجوع‬
How come they're so cheerful?
‫ما بالهم مبتهجين هكذا؟‬
You're quick on the uptake, mister! Everyone here looks happy, right?!
‫إنك دقيق الملاحظة يا سيدي، الجميع يبدون سعيدين، صحيح؟‬
It's slightly different from Okobore Town in Kuri.
‫الوضع مختلف عن بلدة أوكوبوري في مقاطعة كوري‬
Amongst all the species, only humans can laugh!
‫نحن المخلوقات الوحيدة القادرة على الضحك هكذا‬
Yeah!
‫أجل‬
♪ That's why you just gotta laugh! ♪
‫لهذا السبب علينا أن نضحك ونضحك‬
Pardon us!
‫نرجو المعذرة‬
– Shogun Orochi!
‫أوروتشي-ساما‬
Don't be reserved! Raise your heads!
‫لا داعي للرسميات، ارفعوا رؤوسكم‬
Now, what's for dinner?
‫والآن، ما قائمة العشاء الليلة؟‬
Yes! Everything is ready!
‫أمرك، كل شيء جاهز‬
Bring it in!
‫احضروا الطعام‬
We slaughtered the chickens we bred in the beautiful environs of Orochi Farm,
‫ذبحنا الدجاج الذي نربّيه في ضواحي مزرعة أوروتشي البديعة‬
then parboiled them...
‫وغليناها على نار هادئة‬
No! I don't feel like chicken!
‫كلا، لا أريد تناول الدجاج‬
Yes, my lord! We'll discard them!
‫حاضر، سنتخلص منها‬
Take it away!
‫خذوها‬
Next!
‫التالي‬
These fresh, delicious vegetables...
‫خضروات طازجة لذيذة‬
I don't want them!
‫لا أريدها‬
Yes, my lord! We'll throw them out!
‫حاضر‬
Next!
‫التالي‬
We present some of the finest, fattiest saury available!
‫سمك الإسقمري الدسم والشهي‬
I like saury!
‫أحب سمك الإسقمري‬
And tuna sashimi!
‫وساشيمي التونة‬
Yeah! Nothing beats tuna! Tuna!
‫أجل، لا ألذّ من التونة‬
And we have selected a variety of sake from across Wano...
‫جلبنا أفخم أنواع الساكي من شتّى أنحاء وانو‬
I get it!
‫فهمت‬
Of course you have plenty of sake to go around!
‫من البديهي أن تجلبوا أفخم أنواع الساكي‬
But how about women?
‫ولكن ماذا عن النساء؟‬
Of course, right away!
‫جلبنا نساء بالطبع‬
Good! Good!
‫جيد، جيد‬
Mom, I'm hungry!
‫أمي، أنا جائع‬
Me, too!
‫وأنا أيضًا‬
My tooth fell out from malnutrition!
‫سقط ضرسي من قلّة التغذية‬
Not like you have any food to chew anyway!
‫لا يوجد طعام لتمضغيه أصلًا‬
Now, Tonoyasu, who is this ronin fellow?
‫من هذا الرونين يا تونوياسو؟‬
He has three swords belted on!
‫إنه يحمل ثلاثة سيوف‬
You're right! Three swords!
‫معك حق، يحمل ثلاثة سيوف‬
And they're all long swords!
‫وجميعها سيوف طويلة‬
Are you trying to be funny?!
‫أهذا جزء من استعراض هزلي؟‬
Whoa, whoa! I admire this gentleman!
‫ويحكم، أنا معجب بحضرته‬
Oh no! I'm sorry to hear you've had this weirdo following you around.
‫عجبًا، أشفق عليك لوجود رجل غريب يتبعك أينما ذهبت أيها الرونين‬
Wrong! I'm the world's greatest sycophant!
‫أنا أعظم متملّق في العالم‬
Right, handsome?!
‫أليس كذلك أيها الفاتن؟‬
He sure is, but look! He has that frightful expression!
‫فهمت، ولكن انظر إلى ملامحه المخيفة‬
Come on, young man. Drop the scary look.
‫هيا أيها الشاب، لا تُظهر هذه الملامح المخيفة‬
Give us a smile!
‫ابتسم هكذا‬
Good things happen, even in a miserable hole like Ebisu!
‫فقد حلّ الخير على بلدة إبيسو‬
Wait, are you saying he paid this town a visit?!
‫حلّ الخير؟ أتقصدين أنّ حضرته أتى لبلدتنا؟‬
That's right! The Witching Hour Boy paid us another visit!
‫حلّ علينا الخير البارحة إذ زارنا فتى ساعة السحر‬
That's great!
‫هذا رائع‬
Yeah, he always comes by when we're in trouble!
‫أجل، يزورنا كلما اشتد بنا الجوع وتقطّعت بنا السُبل‬
We don't even know who he is.
‫إلا أنَّ لا أحد يعرف هويته‬
He appears at the witching hour
‫يظهر في ساعة السحر‬
and steals money from the rich, evil people of the capital...
‫ويسرق أموال الأثرياء الفاسدين في العاصمة‬
1,000 Gold
‫ألف ذهب‬
He leaves the money at poor tenements and disappears.
‫ثم يرميها عند أبواب منازل الفقراء ويختفي‬
I wonder who he is.
‫من يكون يا تُرى؟‬
Thank goodness, thank goodness!
‫الشكر له، الشكر له‬
Fortune comes to those who laugh!
‫الحظ يأتي لمن يضحك‬
So we pooled our money to ourselves a treat!
‫لذا اشترينا هدية لأنفسنا‬
Oh! What kind of treat?!
‫حقًّا؟ ما هذه الهدية؟‬
Here it is!
‫إنها هنا‬
You see?
‫أرأيت؟‬
This is it!
‫هذا ما اشتريناه‬
Please have a cup!
‫اشرب هذا الكوب...‬
You should have some, too!
‫يا حضرة الرونين‬
It's clear water!
‫إنها مياه نقية‬
We bought it with the money we were given!
‫اشتريناها بتلك الأموال‬
No, I shouldn't...
‫لا، أنا...‬
Don't worry!
‫لا تقلق‬
This water's clean, so you won't get a tummy ache!
‫إنها مياه نقية ولن تؤلمك معدتك إن شربتها‬
Yasu brought you here, so you must be a good man!
‫أتيت برفقة ياسو-سان، لذا لا بدّ أنك رجل لطيف‬
Don't be shy!
‫لا تخجل‬
Go ahead and drink! Everyone has the right to have some!
‫هيا اشرب يحق للجميع شرب مياه نقية‬
♪ Delicious water! ♪
‫مياه عذبة‬
♪ Clear water! ♪
‫مياه نقية‬
Good huh?! It seeps into every fiber of your being, right?!
‫أليست عذبة؟ أليست منعشة تروي العطش؟‬
There's that scary look again!
‫ها أنت مجددًا، صارت ملامحك مخيفة‬
Smile, or fortune won't smile on you!
‫ابتسم وإلا لن يبتسم الحظ لك‬
In this country, we call everyone's smiling face
‫تسمى الوجوه البشوشة في هذه البلاد...‬
an Ebisu grin, mister!
‫إبيسو غاو = "ابتسامة إبيسو" وهي ما يتصف بها إله الحظ إبيسو‬
That's why this place is called Ebisu!
‫لهذا تُدعى هذه البلدة بإبيسو‬
We won't let poverty get us down!
‫لن يحبطنا الفقر‬
♪ Crying won't cure your poverty! ♪ ♪ So, you just gotta laugh! ♪
‫لن يحل البكاء معضلة فقرنا، لهذا علينا أن نضحك ونضحك‬
♪ You just gotta laugh! ♪
‫علينا أن نضحك ونضحك‬
Enough waiting! Let me see them!
‫نفد صبري، دعوني أراهن‬
Just a moment, my lord!
‫انتظر رجاءً يا مولاي‬
A-Are you pleased with them, my lord?
‫هـ-هل حاز جمالهن على رضى سعادتك؟‬
They're... gorgeous!
‫إنهن... آسرات‬
Simply superb! Let's start the banquet immediately!
‫عظيم، لنبدأ السهرة الآن‬
Drink!
‫اشربن‬
Dance!
‫ارقصن‬
Sing!
‫غنّين‬
Don't hold back!
‫لا داعي للرسميات‬
Kurozumi Orochi Shogun of Wano
‫كوروزومي أوروتشي‬ ‫شوغن بلاد وانو‬
I have arrived, my lord...
‫أنا هنا-أرينسو‬
Oh, Komurasaki! I've missed you!
‫يا كوموراساكي، اشتقتُ إليك‬
And I, you...
‫وأنا أيضًا-أرينسو...‬
my lord.
‫يا مولاي‬
Oh, y-you did?!
‫حـ-حقًّا؟‬
You did?!
‫حقًّا؟‬
Traffy, what brings you here?
‫تراو؟ ما الذي أتى بك؟‬
We have an emergency. You need to hide, Black Leg.
‫إنها حالة طارئة، اختبئ أيها الساق السوداء-يا‬
This about the fight earlier? If they come back, I'll just beat them again.
‫هل للأمر علاقة بالشجار السابق؟ سأهزمهم إن عادوا مجددًا‬
That's not it.
‫لم أقصد ذلك‬
The guys that are coming know our faces!
‫ثمة أشخاص يعرفون وجوهنا قادمون نحونا‬
Is it Hawkins?
‫أتقصد هوكينز؟‬
It wouldn't be so bad if it was just him...
‫ليته وحده‬
The six strongest headliners are known as the Soaring Six.
‫يسمى أقوى ستة من الشينوتشي بالتوبي روبّو‬
Two of them are coming here.
‫واثنان منهم قادمان‬
Two?
‫اثنان؟‬
The first is Page One from the Soaring Six.
‫الأول هو بيج ون‬
Page One Soaring Six, Beast Pirates
‫بيج ون‬ ‫توبي روبو في قراصنة الوحوش‬
The Soaring Six... Page One...
‫توبي روبو؟ بيج ون؟‬
The other one is X Drake from the Soaring Six.
‫الثاني هو ديس دريك‬
Drake...
‫دريك؟‬
He's from the Worst Generation...
‫إنه من الجيل الأسوأ‬
Page One, why do we have to do this?
‫بيج ون، لماذا علينا التكفل بهذه المهمة؟‬
X Drake Soaring Six, Beast Pirates
‫ديس دريك‬ ‫توبي روبو في قراصنة الوحوش‬
To set an example, I guess...
‫لجعله عبرة للجميع‬
We've got to show them what happens when you cross the Beast Pirates in Wano.
‫يجب أن يعرف من في بلاد وانو...‬
So, why are you here...
‫إذًا فلماذا أنت هنا يا هوكينز؟‬
I'm looking for someone.
‫أتيت للبحث عن رجل‬
You'll get more than you bargained for with this job, Drake...
‫ستحظى بأكثر مما تريده في هذه المهمة يا دريك‬
Have you thought about my offer from earlier, Boss?
‫هل فكرت في عرضي السابق يا سيدي؟‬
If you're gonna break out, take me with you!
‫إن كنت ستهرب، فخذني معك‬
I'll do anything!
‫سأنفذ أيًّا مما تطلبه‬
If we join forces, we'll be unstoppable!
‫إن تحالفنا، فلن نهاب كائنًا من كان‬
Shut up already! Why don't you team up with Jaggy?!
‫اخرس، اذهب وتحالف مع المسنّن‬
You mean Kid?
‫أتقصد الوغد كيد؟‬
No way. His reputation is terrible.
‫كلا، فسمعته في الحضيض‬
Did you hear he tried to take down Big Mom?!
‫ألا تعلم؟ خاض قتالًا مع بيغ مام محاولًا الإطاحة بها‬
Rumor has it one of her subordinates— not her—took his arm,
‫وتفيد الإشاعات أنّ أحد أتباع بيغ مام بتر ذراعه ثم هرب يجرّ أذيال الهزيمة‬
Rumor? It's pathetic to listen to that kinda crap.
‫إشاعات؟ حالك ميؤوس منه حقًّا‬
Nah, I heard it from a trusted source, Boss.
‫لا، سمعتها من مصدر موثوق يا سيدي‬
Who is this source?
‫ومن هذا المصدر الموثوق؟‬
I've never tried to take down Big Mom!
‫أنا لم أحاول أبدًا الإطاحة ببيغ مام‬
K-K-K-Kid!
‫كـ-كـ-كـ-كيد‬
I wounded one of her Sweet Commanders,
‫أصبتُ أحد قادة الحلوى في طاقمها‬
took what I wanted, and left!
‫وأخذت مبتغاي منها وخرجت‬
B-B-B-But your arm...
‫لـ-لـ-لـ-لكن ذراعك...‬
I'd already lost it before that, in a battle against the Red Hair Pirates.
‫بُترت ذراعي قبل ذلك بمدة، في خضم معركتي مع قراصنة أحمر الشعر‬
Any other questions?!
‫هل من أسئلة أخرى؟‬
None.
‫لا‬
Then, let me tell you something! You listen up, too, you stupid monkey!
‫إذًا أصغِ إلى ما سأقوله جيدًا، وأنت كذلك أيها القرد الأحمق‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
I'm the one who's gonna take down Kaido and get the glory!
‫من سيسقط كايدو وينتزع جاه المجد هو أنا‬
No, I am!
‫بل أنا‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Everyone, the Fire Festival is nearly upon us!
‫هيا هيا، اقترب موعد مهرجان النار‬
Let's consider this party the opening act!
‫لنجعل هذه الحفلة افتتاحية‬
Go ahead and indulge yourselves!
‫هيا استمتعوا‬
This is Wano!
‫فهذه بلاد وانو‬
We may as well be in heaven!
‫لا تظنوا أنّها الجنة‬
Eat and drink to your heart's content!
‫كلوا حتى التخمة واشربوا حتى الثمالة‬
They're approaching from the southeast in a massive ship!
‫ثمة سفينة ضخمة تقترب الآن من الجنوب الشرقي‬
She actually came!
‫إذًا فأتت حقًّا‬
Blast them!
‫اغرقوها في البحر‬
Don't let her enter the country!
‫إياكم أن تدخل البلاد‬
But there is a problem...
‫ولكن ثمة مشكلة...‬
Koi are pulling their ship and they're charing ahead!
‫إنهم يتقدمون بسرعة بفضل جر أسماك الشبوط لسفينتهم‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
How do they know how to climb the waterfall?!
‫أنّى لهم معرفة كيفية صعود الشلال؟‬
Well, the Big Mom Pirates are known for gathering good intel.
‫هذا لأن قراصنة بيغ مام لديهم الكفاءة بجمع المعلومات‬
Shut it! I don't care!
‫اخرس، لا يهمني ذلك‬
We knew they were coming!
‫كنا نعلم أنهم قادمون‬
Just sink them already!
‫اغرقوهم حالًا‬
That old bag! I'm sure she remembers that I warned her...
‫تلك العجوز الشمطاء، متأكد أنها تتذكر تحذيري لها‬
I'll kill you if you come here, Linlin!
‫سأقتلكِ إن أتيتِ يا لينلين‬
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat...
‫لن تفلت مني يا قبعة القش‬